[WOMAN] We love it!
Oh, thank you.
[WOMAN] We still need one more approval.
Billy, Jordan,
I'd like you to meet Mr. Alvin Ramirez.
Do we really have to do this, dude?
Once LoveList becomes successful,
even Oliver will benefit from it.
And think about the women
at Angels of Grace.
[MULTIPLE PHONES CHIMING]
Alvin! You better stop signing that.
Gia?
- Let's go!
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- [GIA GRUNTS]
[ALVIN] You know, Billy, trying
to reconnect with you was a mistake.
Deal is off.
[TONI] Who would even do this?
[MARJ] It has to be Valerie.
Did you have anything to do with
LoveList getting hacked?
Am I the only person with
a grudge against you?
- [VALERIE GROANS]
- Ma'am!
- [WOMAN] Ma'am!
- [VALERIE CRYING]
You shouldn't have hit Val.
After everything she said
about me and my family?
Do you think I'd just let it slide?
[ENGINE MISFIRING]
What's wrong?
Let me do it.
Relax.
[GRUNTS]
[ENGINE MISFIRES]
It's probably an engine problem.
I think you'll have to get it fixed
at the auto repair shop.
[SCREAMS, GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Are you done?
- Come on, smile.
- [CLICKS TONGUE]
[JORDAN] Psst.
Stop!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
We're gonna fix this.
Trust me.
Hey.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry about your car.
We'll pick it up tomorrow.
Just go home for now.
Okay.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] Do you think
we can track down the hacker?
I can try.
Thank you.
Dude!
A shooting star. Did you see it?
Make a wish.
I can't let a shooting star
decide LoveList's future.
Well, unless it invests in us.
That'd be nice.
Impossible.
I don't want our efforts to go to waste.
You know, since I already
invested my money,
let's just do it.
Come hell or high water,
we will launch LoveLine.
How?
You no longer have an investor.
I'll pawn the house. Double mortgage!
- [FLICKS] You're nuts!
- Ow!
This is what you need.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
[BILLY] Shooting star,
my wish
is that we can catch that darn hacker.
Will you grant my wish, shooting star?
Please, shooting star.
[IN TINY VOICE] Okay.
Thank you, shooting star.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[BILLY] Auntie Pres?
[PRECIOUS] Oh, Billy!
Come here. Let's eat.
- Hi, Auntie Pres.
- Let's eat.
Oh, where's Oliver?
He's already sleeping.
Then why are there three plates?
Didn't you see my message?
We have a visitor.
Who?
[PRECIOUS] Just there.
- Come.
- Ms. Billy!
[ABI] Hello!
Abi!
I went to the center earlier.
I wanted to thank you
because our conversation
really helped me a lot.
- [BILLY] Mm…
- But you weren't there
so Ms. Precious became
the victim of my endless talking.
That's why I brought her with me.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
It's okay. You don't have to thank me.
I usually do that, maybe once
a week, at the center.
I like helping people.
I'm glad I could help you.
Oh, I'm so glad she's my idol.
You help a lot of people.
But, Ms. Billy, who helps you?
I saw what happened with LoveList.
I just got worried,
so that's one of the reasons why I'm here.
- Mm.
- Also, have you seen this?
Here.
[VALERIE] Hi, guys.
So Doc Rosie was just here,
and, yes, this happened.
[WHIMPERS]
It's still a bit swollen right now, guys,
but I think it's getting better.
I mean, I still look pretty, thank God.
So, yeah.
Long story short, guys,
there was an issue
with that deranged CEO
who won't leave me alone!
I didn't even do anything!
You know what, Ms. Billy?
I think
she's just messing with you.
She wants you to react.
And once you do,
she'll make content out of it.
I've been taking care
of this company for years.
I'm not gonna back down now.
- Mm.
- All right.
Remember, it's okay to fight back,
but not in that way.
I'm sorry, Auntie Pres.
I'm just mad at people
who can't fight without hiding.
I can't just let them get away with this.
The moment I find out
who started all this,
I'll do everything I can
to put them in jail.
They don't know
what I'm like when I'm angry.
- I'm sorry, Abi.
- [ABI] Hmm?
I'm sorry about this.
I'm not really good at handling my anger.
Oh, Ms. Billy, don't worry about me.
I'm perfectly fine.
If I could,
I'd help you in any way possible.
And I mean, anything.
Enough of that. Come on and eat.
You haven't even taken a bite.
[PRECIOUS] Keep eating, dear.
Come on.
Hey.
Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude.
Thanks again for blocking
the LoveSpeak hacker.
[EXHALES] Dude…
It's so hard to trace this hacker.
They used proxies, cloaked IPs,
layered encryption, everything.
Whoever it was,
they're still not stopping.
People are still reposting the same video.
I think it's the same person.
What do you think?
Aren't these like the troll accounts
we had on LoveSpeak?
- Can you check it out?
- You're right.
I noticed too.
Okay. I'll take care of it.
Ah, dude, I'm sorry.
Oliver's Family Day
will be this Saturday, okay?
Don't forget about it.
Of course. All right now.
I'll take care of this.
Good night. Thank you.
Sis, it's Family Day tomorrow.
1:00 p.m. sharp.
Yes, sir. I'd never forget.
Jordan is coming too.
- See you.
- Bye, sis!
- I'm gonna miss you!
- Wow! I'll miss you too!
Bye-bye!
Take care, mister.
[VAN DOOR CLOSES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Auntie Pres?
[PRECIOUS] I'm coming!
Yes? What is it?
Auntie, did you see
my keys here last night?
Do you know where I put them?
Well, those are mine.
Maybe you left them in your car
or at the office?
I don't think so.
I remember using them last night
when I opened the door.
You were cooking at the time.
Or… was it already open?
I'm sorry, Auntie.
- [PRECIOUS] Uh…
- I can't remember.
A lot happened last night.
All right. Okay, I got it.
Here's what we'll do.
You can use my keys for now,
and I'll try to look for yours
when I get home.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
- Okay, okay.
- Take care.
- Love you.
- Love you!
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello? Dude.
Mission accomplished, dude.
Your wish
is my command.
Good news?
This hacker thinks he's a pro.
But I'm a lot better.
He tried to log in earlier,
so I sent a fake password reset link.
I got his location!
Finally!
Mm. Thank you, dude. Thank you.
You're welcome. Anything for you, dude.
Miss, there are no grounds to file a case
based only on your suspicions.
If you want, we can file
an incident report instead.
I understand that suspicion
is not enough grounds.
But I've suffered actual damage
to my company, my finances,
and my reputation.
We have the location
of the account involved.
They can respond to any question
we may have for them.
Can you trace the troll's identity?
Miss, this is just GPS data.
It's not admissible
without a chain of custody.
You will first need
to file a formal complaint
in order to obtain a court order.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
How did you get the troll's location?
If you don't have permission,
that's illegal.
Sir!
This person hacked the accounts
on our app.
Isn't that illegal too?
We know that.
But what you did was
counter-hacking or phishing.
They can sue you too,
under the Cybercrime Law
and Data Policy Act.
That's right.
Are you saying that
there's nothing we can do?
Well, you didn't really do it legally.
And you still don't have proof.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
[CAR LOCKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Miss!
Where you going?
Bye, beautiful!
[CALOY] Yeah.
They can change passwords all they want.
She can even block me from her app.
I can still hack it, anyway.
Just tell me
if you want to hack LoveList again.
I can post stuff on
Benilda Cariño's account too.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CALOY] You want that?
All right.
[CALOY MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY]
Boss! B-b-b--Oh, wow.
Bo-- Good morning. Hi.
- People are waiting downstairs.
- All right, I'll be there.
You sure?
- Yeah.
- Can you be there today?
Good morning.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
- Dude.
- Hello?
Jordan, I've been calling you.
Sorry, I fell asleep.
I'm outside the troll's house.
What?!
Dude! That's dangerous.
Leave now!
The police said they needed proof, right?
Then I'll give them what they want.
Benilda, you're going too far.
If you don't leave there,
I won't be friends with you anymore.
- [CALL DROPS]
- Billy.
Hello?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC TURNS SUSPENSEFUL]
[CALOY CHUCKLING, CRUNCHING SNACKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CALOY] Hey! Who's there?
Who's there?
Hey!
Miss!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CALOY] Hey! Give that to me.
Delete the picture you took.
Give me your phone.
Don't come any closer.
I'll scream if you come any closer.
You'll scream? Go ahead. Do it!
I can even help you!
- Give me your phone!
- Who were you talking to earlier?
Who's giving you these orders?
Why would I tell you?
Huh?
Ms. Benilda Cariño?
Give me your phone.
I'll delete the picture.
Otherwise, you'll only get hurt.
- [YELPS]
- I said give that to me!
Get off me!
Help!
[YELPS]
- [GRUNTS]
- That hurt!
- Come here!
- Help me, please!
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
- You little…
- [SCREAMS]
Help me, please!
[CRYING]
Who are you?!
[GRUNTS]
Jordan!
[YELPS]
Ha!
- [CALOY] C'mon!
- Jordan!
- [GRUNTS] Come on!
- Help, please!
Jordan!
[GROANS]
That's enough!
[GRUNTS]
Someone, help us!
[GROANS]
- [FLESH RIPS]
- [SCREAMS]
Leave!
Well?
[BILLY WHIMPERING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
- I told you to leave!
- [BILLY] That's enough!
Enough! Jordan, we need to go!
Help!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR SCRAPING]
[CELL PHONE BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello?
We've got a problem.
We've got a problem!
- [PATROLMAN] Hands up! Get down!
- [CALOY] Wait.
- [GRUNTS]
- Stop fighting back!
- Slowly! Slowly!
- Hey!
I can do it.
There we go!
Does it hurt?
I can handle it.
You should be thankful
that it's not life-threatening.
You only needed four stitches, but still.
Just rest, okay?
- It's just a scratch.
- Hmm.
The troll has been caught.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
His name is Caloy Toledo.
Okay.
However, he doesn't seem to know
who gave the orders.
Can't he just describe the person?
What they look like?
Nothing?
He said he never saw them personally.
The only way they communicate
is through the messaging app.
The payment is left at his door.
The police are checking
if they can see any identity on the app.
They are also checking
the CCTV footage in the area.
I really hope it's not Val.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry, dude.
I'm sorry you got dragged into this mess.
[SIGHS]
What are friends for?
Ouch! [GROANS]
Billy!
- What did you do to me?
- Oh, hush you!
- You're being silly!
- Ouch! Ouch!
- Oh, sorry! [CHUCKLES]
- [CELLPHONE RINGING]
I'm sorry!
Oh my God, dude.
Oliver's Family Day is tomorrow.
Oh, yeah!
No, I'll explain it to him!
I'll handle it. You rest.
I'll take care of it.
You should go home.
- I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
Nothing hurts?
- Do you need anything else?
- Nope, nothing hurts.
I'm fine.
- I'm okay.
- Let me see.
[BOTH YELPS]
Just kidding. Call me
if you need anything.
Thanks, dude.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Good afternoon, everyone!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[PRINCIPAL] Thank you!
Thank you for spending your time today
to celebrate our Family Day!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
The troll has already been caught.
But what if the person who's
paying Caloy has more people?
[PRINCIPAL] And most of all…
Don't worry, Aunt Pres.
I'll hunt them down.
Caloy won't get off either.
I'm getting worried, Billy.
[PRINCIPAL] So let's cherish
this moment together.
- [OLIVER] Billy! Billy!
- Hmm?
Where's Jordan? It's about to start!
I'm sorry, but Jordan is injured.
- It's only us today.
- Don't worry about it!
- Your sister and I are here!
- See? Present!
[PRINCIPAL]
Parents and guardians, welcome!
Let's enjoy the program
and let the games begin!
- [CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING]
We actually need five trios again
for this game!
We already have two.
Billy! Auntie!
Can we please join this game?
What?
Oh, no, Auntie Pres is injured!
Let's just wait for another pairs game,
then we'll win again.
I promise, okay?
- There will be more games.
- [TEACHER] We need three more trios!
Hold on!
- We'll join!
- Jordan!
- [JORDAN] Just in time!
- [OLIVER] Yes!
- [PRECIOUS CHUCKLES]
- What is he doing here?
You're not supposed to be here!
- Please!
- Are you a doctor?
Please?
- [CHUCKLES]
- Hey, little dude.
- Are you ready to win?
- Yes! Super!
- They will all lose to us.
- Yeah, they will.
- ["KULIMLIM" BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
- Come on!
Slow down!
[CHEERING]
[OLIVER] Come on! Go!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER, CHEERING]
C'mon, Oliver! Do it again!
There! Bite hard!
- C'mon!
- Swallow it!
[BILLY] Good job!
[ALL CHEERING]
[OLIVER SHOUTING
AND EXCLAIMING EXCITEDLY]
[JORDAN GRUNTS]
- Keep your balance!
- We can do it.
[ONLOOKERS AND CONTESTANTS
EXCLAIM EXCITEDLY]
- Dude.
- Your wound is bleeding!
- C'mon, Billy!
- It's fine!
- C'mon!
- Billy!
- No!
- [JORDAN] Come on!
- Jump!
- Come on, Billy!
Jump!
Are you okay?
I'll be fine!
[CHEERING]
- Yes!
- We did it!
- We won!
- Wow.
Thank you!
[PRINCIPAL] You're welcome!
- Ouch!
- [YELPS]
Stop that!
You're so stubborn.
I told you not to come.
- Look at what happened!
- I'm fine!
- Your wound was bleeding!
- What's important is that we won!
Okay.
So you feel fine?
Why am I even doing this?
[CHUCKLES]
- All done?
- Does it hurt? Hold on, let me fix it.
Hey, by the way,
have you seen my house keys?
I might have left them at your place.
Hmm.
I haven't.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Did you lose them?
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Thanks, dude.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] Okay, bye, Auntie Pres!
- [OLIVER] Bye!
- [PRECIOUS] Bye!
[BILLY] Oliver?
I'll just check on Jordan, okay?
He might be running a fever.
I'll be back soon.
[OLIVER] Do you want me
to go with you?
[BILLY] No, I'll be fine.
Go and shower, then rest.
- All right, bye!
- [BILLY] Bye! [SMOOCHES]
Go ahead and shower, okay? You're sweaty!
- Bye, love you!
- I'll be quick, Auntie!
[PRECIOUS] I'll leave your food
in the fridge, okay?
- [BILLY] All right, thank you!
- [PRECIOUS] Okay, bye, take care!
[OLIVER] Bye!
[OLIVER] You were amazing
earlier, Auntie Pres.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you here
because you're feeling guilty?
Do you really think I would do that?
I'm here because I want to
make it up to Jordan.
We just have to be more prepared
and more careful.
It's nothing.
[VALERIE] I'm doing this for you.
I just wanted to clear the air between us.
This caller seems to know you.
How can I support you today?
Oh my gosh, Ms. Billy!
Is that really you?
Must be nice.
The truth always has its way
of revealing itself.